Yuhan Liu

Address: Pengkang Building 206, 28 Xianning W Rd, Xi'an, China Email: lyh6560@stu.xjtu.edu.cn, photo12112112121@gmail.com

Homepage: yuhan.info Last updated: April 8, 2023

Research Interests

My greatest interest lies in natural language processing, specifically in natural language generation, knowledge graphs, reasoning, graph neural networks, and social network analysis. Besides, I have done research in various areas such as Twitter bot detection, graph representation learning, and multi-object detection(computer vision). Now I'm working on the controllable generation of pretrained language models.

Education

Xi'an Jiaotong University, Xi'an, Shaanxi, China (member of the C9 league in China) 2020.09 - present B.E. in Automation Science and Informatics

GPA: 94.3/100, rank 1rst/33 Advisor: Prof. Minnan Luo

The Special Class for the Gifted Young / Honors Youth Program,

2018.09 - present

Publications (* indicates equal contribution)

[2] BotMoE: Twitter Bot Detection with Community-Aware Mixtures of Modal-Specific Experts.

Yuhan Liu, Zhaoxuan Tan, Heng Wang, Shangbin Feng, Qinghua Zheng, Minnan Luo.

In Proceedings of SIGIR, 2023.

[1] TwiBot-22: Towards Graph-Based Twitter Bot Detection.

Shangbin Feng*, Zhaoxuan Tan, Herun Wan*, Ningnan Wang*, Zilong Chen*, Binchi Zhang*, Qinghua Zheng, Wenqian Zhang, Zhenyu Lei, Shujie Yang, Xinshun Feng, Qingyue Zhang, Hongrui Wang, <u>Yuhan Liu</u>, Yuyang Bai, Heng Wang, Zijian Cai, Yanbo Wang, Lijing Zheng, Zihan Ma, Jundong Li, Minnan Luo. *In Proceedings of the NeurIPS Datasets and Benchmarks Track, 2022.*

Honors and Awards

National Scholarship	2022
National Scholarship	2021
Dean's List, Xi'an Jiaotong University	2021
Outstanding Award, National English Competition for College Students	2020
Dean's List, Xi'an Jiaotong University	2020
First Prize, The Chinese Mathematics Competitions	2019

Experience

Research Assistant of the **LUD lab**, focusing on graph-based Twitter bot detection and knowledge graph embedding learning. Advisor: Minnan Luo @ Xi'an Jiaotong University, China

Vice President of XJTU VTOL club, leading a team focusing in 3D object detection. Advisor: Tonghui Wu@ Xi'an Jiaotong University

National Undergraduate Training Programs for Innovation and Entrepreneurship, Xi'an Jiaotong
University
2022.5-

Knowledge graph representation learning based on pretrained language models

Advisor: Minnan Luo @ Xi'an Jiaotong University, China

CHINA ROBOT COMPETITION, Xi'an Jiaotong University

2021.10-2021.11

As the leader of the team, I implemented a complete software to realize multi-object detection and communication with the judging machine on Jetson Nano (a small, powerful computer designed to power entry-level edge AI applications) with my teammates.

Advisor: Tonghui Wu @ Xi'an Jiaotong University, China

Research Experience, Xi'an Jiaotong University

2021.10-2022.2

Complete semantic segmentation part for a multi-modal project about medical image processing

Advisor: Shaoyi Du @ Xi'an Jiaotong University, China

National Undergraduate Training Programs for Innovation and Entrepreneurship, Xi'an Jiaotong University 2021.3-7

Fast Boolean Operation of Triangular Network Model Based on GPU

Advisor: Yijun Yang @ Xi'an Jiaotong University, China

Services

Reviewer for NeurIPS, Datasets and Benchmarks Track

2022

Skills

Programming Languages:

-Proficient: Python, MATLAB, C/C++

Tools and Frameworks: PyTorch, LATEX, Visual Studio, MobaXTerm, Git, ssh, Vim

Natural Languages: Mandarin (native), English (fluent)